[ Creaking ]
[ Person Exhaling ]
[ Dog Barking ]
[ Man On TV Chattering ] I 'm working my triceps .
I 'm working the back of my calves , and I 'm working my heart .
[ Chattering Continues ] [ Wind Chimes Tinkling ]
[ Chomping ]
whole body calorie burning . whole body muscle toning . Everything .
Now what about upper body ? All right . We 'll do upper body .
[ Horse Whinnying ]
Now , here 's one of our new movements .
I want you to see the range of motion . Just go to ' ' Hurdle " or ' ' Sprint . "
Look at the sprint that I have .
How many people can get that range of motion ?
Say I wanna dojust my hip flexors or my buttocks even more .
I do what 's called digging .
Look at the range of motion . I use this for a lot ofswimwear models .
Very , very , very important . How ' bout Butt Squeeze ?
Yup . I see you wanted to touch .
That 's a good way - Not this show ! Not touching this show !
[ Rattling ]
[ Children Laughing ]
[ woman Narrating ] Hell is a teenage girl .
[ Laughing Continues ]
[ Birds Chirping ]
[ Narrating Continues ] I guess I 'm not exactly perfect myself .
But at least I have my fans .
I mean , I get letters every day .
Mostly from perverts and chesters ,
but still ...
I 'm kinda the shit .
[ women Shouting ]
Rec time started five minutes ago , Needy .
Grassy-ass , Raymundo .
Sometimes , the letters are from people who say they 're praying for me .
They tell me everything will be okay if I just accept Jesus Christ into my heart .
I say the words , but nothing ever happens .
Nobody comes back .
Nobody gets off the cross .
welcome to the Mental Olympics .
They 're big on recreation here .
Supposedly , it helps us vent our aggressions .
Oh , yeah !
Personally , I think they 're trying to wear us out ,
keep us sluggish so there won 't be an uprising .
well , those J.V. tactics won 't work against me .
I 'm a kicker .
K-I-C-K-E-R .
It even says so on my chart .
Just one Toast ' Em , huh ?
I like Toast ' Ems . Well , that 's good .
But I 'm not sure a Toast ' Em can provide sufficient energy during your day .
I recommend more complex carbo —
- No , she didn 't ! - I recommend you shut the fuck up !
- All right . - [ Cheering ]
[ woman Shouting ]
Don 't touch me !
[ Screaming ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Panting ]
[ Narrating Continues ] I wasn 't always this cracked .
I used to be normal .
well , as normal as any girl under the influence of teenage hormones .
But after the killings began , I started to feel —
I don 't know -
loose around the edges or something .
♪ ♪ [ Speakers : Muzak ]
God !
I hate this fucking song .
♪ ♪ [ Rock ]
This is where it all went down .
' ' Devil 's Kettle " sounds twisted , I know ,
but the place is just named after a waterfall .
Technically , it 's not a normal waterfall .
It goes into this hole , and it doesn 't come out .
The scientist guys dropped all kinds of things down there ,
but nothing ever surfaces .
Maybe it 's another dimension .
or , you know , just really deep .
♪ ♪ [ Pop ]
Just two months ago , me , Jennifer and my boyfriend , Chip ,
were completely normal people .
we were our yearbook pictures .
Nothing more , nothing less .
♪ one ♪ ♪ I 'm biting my tongue ♪
♪ Two ♪ ♪ He 's kissin ' on you ♪
♪ Three ♪ ♪ oh , why can 't you see ♪
♪ One , two , three , four ♪
[ Narrating Continues ] There 's Jennifer .
only back then , we were tight .
Sisters , practically .
People found it hard to believe that a babe like Jennifer ...
would associate with a dork like me .
Sandbox love never dies .
♪ Dance , dance , dance , dance ♪ ♪ You are the girl ♪
♪ That I 've been dreaming of ♪
You 're totally lesbi-gay .
What ? She 's my best friend .
[ Mock Giggling ]
♪ Ever since I was a little girl ♪
♪ one ♪ ♪ I 'm biting my tongue ♪
♪ Two ♪ ♪ He 's kissing on you ♪ ♪
Hey , Monistat . What 's up , Vagisil ?
You and me are going out tonight . Uh , tonight . Why ?
Because Low Shoulder are playing at Melody Lane .
They 're this indie rock band from the city .
I saw their MySpace page , and the lead singer 's extra salty .
Plus , there 'll be lots of other salty morsels there foryou .
Come on , Needy . I promised Chip that I would hang out with him tonight .
Boo . Cross out Needy .
What time is the show ? I 'll pick you up at 8 : 30 .
My mom has a date with that guy who owns the ham store .
He seems nice .
wear something cute , okay ? Okay .
' ' wear something cute " meant something very specific in Jennifer-speak .
It meant I couldn 't look like a total zero , but I couldn 't upstage her either .
I could expose my stomach , but never my cleavage .
Tits were her trademark .
Those jeans are hella low . I can almost see your front butt .
It 's a rock show . This is my rock look .
Well , I can see , like , your womb , so —
I 've never even heard of Low Shoulder .
which one is Jennifer stalking ? The lead singer .
Girls like her don 't go out with drummers .
- Thanks a lot . - No offense .
She 'd probably make an exception if you were , like , a drummer who 's also the lead singer .
- Like Phil Collins . - Who 's Phil Collins ?
Forget it . He 's seminal , but whatever .
Anyway , this singer guy , Jennifer says he 's extra salty , so -
Salty .
Salty means beautiful .
Well , then you must be soy sauce , babe .
Jennifer 's here .
How do you know ? Needy !
Quit tampooning yourself and get down here .
That 's fucking weird .
Better hurry before she gets annoyed . [ Grunts ]
You always do what Jennifer tells you to do .
No , I don 't . It 's just that I like the same things that she likes .
We have stuff in common . That 's why we 're biffs .
You guys don 't have anything in common .
Yeah. okay , Chip .
Guess who 's got the whip until 11 : 30 .
A 2003 Chrysler Sebring , and it 's all mine .
[ Giggles ] oh , hi , Chip .
[ Sniffs ] It smells like Thai food in here .
- Have you guys been fucking ? - You 're gross .
- You 're gross . You 're gross . - You 're so gross .
Fuck you . Let 's go to the club .
Melody Lane is not a club . It 's a bar .
It 's not even a bar . It 's like a bingo hall with taps .
Eat my ass , Chip . You 're just Jell-O 'cause you 're not invited .
I 'm not jealous . That place is disgusting .
Everyone in there has a mustache . You 're totally Jell-O .
You 're lime-green Jell-O , and you can 't even admit it to yourself .
[ Exhales ] Stop kidnapping my girlfriend .
♪ ♪ [ Rock ] You wish .
[ Needy Narrating ] Chip was right .
Melody Lane is definitely not a club .
[ Pool Balls Clacking ] Clubs are for attractive people in populous urban areas .
Clubs have D.J. ' s and champagne .
[ Man ] As they come around the corner -
[ Needy Narrating ] All we have is a jukebox and a sticker toilet .
♪ You wanna fly Don 't want your feet on the ground ♪
- ♪ You stay up , you won 't come down ♪ - [ Chattering ]
I cannot wait until I 'm old enough to get wasted .
Hey , Jennifer . You look really pretty .
What up , Craig ? [ Laughs ]
He thinks he 's cute enough for me . And that 's why he 's in retard math .
Swing and miss .
Hey , it 's Ahmet from India , that foreign exchange guy .
I wonder if he 's circumcised .
I always wanted to try a sea cucumber .
Ew .
Jennifer Check . Shouldn 't poison yourself with that shit .
Unless you want me to arrest ya for possession .
You 're gonna arrest me ? You 're not even out of the academy yet , Roman .
Two more months . Then I 'm on the force for reals .
Are you , uh — you 're gonna cuff me ?
[ Groans ] Don 't do that .
Okay ? Not here .
[ Needy ] Hey , that 's the band .
[ woman Laughing , Echoing ]
Mmm . You can totally tell they 're from the city .
Yeah , ' cause they 're wearing eyeliner . They look like a bunch of faygos .
Well , you would think that , Roman , because you 're a small-time Gomer .
I wish we had more guys like that in Devil 's Kettle .
All stylish and shit .
[ Tuning ]
[ Jennifer ] I think they need two groupies .
No ! No . Come on . Don 't be so J.V. , Needy .
They 're just boys , morsels . We have all the power .
Don 't you know that ? These things ?
These are like smart bombs . Okay ?
You point them in the right direction , and shit gets real .
Hi . Hi .
Uh — [ Giggling ] we just wanted to meet you or something .
I 'm Jennifer Check , and this is my friend .
Hi . I 'm Nikolai .
This is , uh — These guys are my band .
Low Shoulder . Yeah , we 've heard — I 've heard about you .
You play your instruments really super good .
Thank you . We are professionals .
Hey . Sorry . Could I ask you a question ?
Um , why would you wanna play all the way out here in Devil 's Kettle ?
You live in the city , right ? Yeah .
But , you know , I think it 's really important sometimes to try and connect with our fans ...
in the shitty areas too .
That 's amazing .
[ Chuckling ] Can I , um — Can I buy you a drink ?
Sure . What are we having ?
They have this really awesome 9 / 11 tribute shooter .
It 's red , white and blue , but you have to drink it really fast or it turns brownish .
All right . Well , we 'll drink it fast . okay .
- Okay . - I 'll be right back .
Hey , how - how are you gonna get alcohol ?
Um , I 'll just play Hello Titty with the bartender .
[ Man ] Aw , shit .
Dirk , what about her ?
- who , Jan Brady ? - No , man . Fuck you .
I 'm talking about the one who went to get me a drink . The State Fair Butter Princess .
That 's the one . I don 't know . Are you sure she 's -
Listen , I grew up in a town like this , okay ?
There 's always that girl . They love to show it off , but they do not give it up .
You told us you were from Brooklyn .
My point is , this girl is definitely a virgin , okay ?
- I know girls like that . I 've dated chicks — - I don 't know .
well , we didn 't drive all the way out here for nothing , so- -
- Excuse me . - Hey .
Hey . That 's my best friend that you 're talking about .
And you 're right . She is a virgin .
And that beats sleeping with creeps like you .
[ Groans ]
Tower One isn 't full enough .
Those guys are rank , Jen . Just forget about it .
You know what ? I think the lead singer wants me .
Only because he thinks that you 're a virgin . I heard them talking .
What ? I 'm not even a backdoor virgin anymore , thanks to Roman .
And by the way , that hurts .
I couldn 't even go to Flags the next day .
I had to stay home and sit on a bag of frozen peas .
Oh , my God . [ Electricity Humming ]
[ Nikolai ] Good evening , Devil 's Lake . [ Man ] Devil 's Kettle !
Fuckin ' - A right , it is .
♪ ♪ [ Rock ]
♪ All alone in an empty room ♪
♪ Nothing left but the memories ♪
♪ Of when ♪
♪ I had my best friend ♪
♪ And I don 't know how we ended up here ♪
♪ I don 't know but it 's never been so clear ♪
♪ We made a mistake , dear ♪
♪ And I see ♪
♪ The broken glass in front of me ♪
♪ I see ♪
♪ Your shadow hanging over me ♪
♪ And your face , I can see ♪
♪ Through the trees ♪
♪ I will find you ♪
♪ I will heal ♪
♪ The ruins left inside you ♪
♪ ' Cause I 'm still here breathing now ♪
♪ I 'm still here breathing now ♪
♪ Until I 'm set free ♪
♪ Go quiet through the trees ♪
♪ And I remember how we used to talk ♪
♪ About the places we would go when we grew up ♪
♪ And all that we were gonna find ♪
♪ And I remember watching our seeds grow ♪
♪ And how you cried when you saw the first leaf show ♪ ♪
[ Gasps , Screams ]
[ Glass Shattering ]
[ Man ] Everybody , run !
[ Woman Screams ]
[ Screams ] [ Bones Cracking ]
- [ Screams ] - We can 't get through there !
I know where to go !
[ Screaming ]
Hey . Hey . Jen ?
Hey .
Jennifer ? oh , thank God you guys are all right .
I 've been looking everywhere for you two .
Listen , it 's really dangerous out here .
You wanna head someplace safer , like my van ? What ?
I 'm in survival mode right now , and I want us to get to a familiar place .
And right now , I feel like that 's my van . okay .
Okay , this one 's in shock . Great .
Are you in shock ? Have some of that .
No .
Jennifer ? [ Coughing ]
Hey .
Let 's go , Jennifer ! Let 's go to the van .
I wanna go to your really cool van . Needy , let 's go see his van .
why ? Why should we ?
We have the Sebring . Let 's just get out of here ! Please ?
Needy , stop it ! Just shut up .
[ Needy Narrating ] I watched her get into that van ,
and I knew something awful was going to happen .
He was skinny and twisted and evil ,
like this petrified tree I saw when I was a kid .
[ Panting ]
[ Explosion ] [ Siren Wailing ]
Oh .
[ Beeps ]
[ Cell Phone Chiming ]
- Hey , Niedermeyer . - Oh , thank God you 're there .
What 's wrong ? Jennifer 's gone .
She ran off with that rock band , and Melody Lane burned down .
You 're okay , right ? Uh , yeah .
But there was this huge stampede ,
and all the people that fainted got run over ,
and you could hear their bones breaking .
And the people — [ Sobs ]
like , the people on fire just smelled like —
This is crazy . Jennifer 's still with those creeps .
They took her in their spooky van with the windows all blacked out .
- Did you get the make and model ? - I don 't know , Chip . An ' 89 Rapist ?
She 's still in there . We have to go find her .
Who cares about Jennifer and those douche bags ...
with their douche bag haircuts and their man-scara ?
People just burned to death .
[ Doorbell Ringing ] Oh , cheese and fries . There 's somebody here !
I 'm all alone . I 'm freaked out .
- Where is your mom ? - Swing shift .
Stay on the phone with me , okay ?
Needy , do you want me to come over or something ?
I don 't know . Maybe .
[ Chip ] Needy ?
Okay , so now there 's no one here .
That 's so strange .
Maybe I 'm going crazy .
It 's probably nothing .
Look , I 'll call you later . Okay .
[ Faint Thumping ]
[ Floorboards Creaking ]
[ Hinges Squeak ]
[ water Dripping ]
[ Pipes Squeaking ]
[ Screams ] Hi .
[ Dripping ]
Jen .
What happened ?
Jen ?
[ Refrigerator Door opens ]
Um —
My mom got that at Boston Market , and I 'm — I 'm not supposed to -
[ Roaring ]
[ Gagging ]
[ Retching ]
[ Giggling ]
Jennifer . Jennifer ?
Jennifer .
[ Giggling Continues ]
[ Panting ]
Are you scared ?
[ Siren Wailing ]
[ Door opens ] Jennifer !
[ Woman on Radio , Faint ]
Another body under here !
♪ ♪ [ Rock ]
I heard Needy and Jennifer were there ,
and they had to fight their way out with a machete .
Look , she 's not even moving .
It 's called post-traumatic stress disorder .
My dad was in operation Enduring Freedom ,
and he totally , like , stopped talking for , like , months .
I 'll be Perfect Prom Betty , and you be her .
Why do I have to be Ugly Ashley ?
Ow ! What 's wrong , Jennifer ?
Don 't tell my mom about this . She 'll make me a shot .
I never tell on you .
Where 's it at , Monistat ?
- You 're all right . - Yeah . Why wouldn 't I be ?
'Cause last night at my house , you were —
You do have a tendency to over-react .
Remember when we were in Girl Scout camp , and you thought that there was an earthquake ,
but it was just two guys with a ghetto blaster ?
People died , Jennifer .
It 's , like , all over the news . National news .
Anybody that we know ? We know everyone .
Sucks to be them , I guess .
What is wrong with you ? What 's wrong with you ?
Besides the obvious surface flaws .
[ Needy Narrating ] I knew it was real .
I 'd been up all night , scrubbing the carnage off the linoleum .
[ Crying ]
Shoot .
Please don 't talk to yourself .
It 's one of your more freakish Needy behaviors ...
and it makes us both look like total gaylords .
Ew . Fuck . You need a mani bad .
You should find a Chinese chick to buff your situation .
[ Door Closes ]
This is a dark , dark day ...
for Devil 's Kettle .
And believe me you , I have lived through some —
some pretty heavy stuff .
We lost eight precious students ...
including Ahmet from India ,
several parents ...
and our beloved Spanish teacher ,
Señorita Erickson .
No way . Erickson ate shit ?
Now more than ever , put aside your teenage concerns ...
about who 's a cool dude , or who 's a ho .
we can 't let that damn fire win .
It already won .
God bless you kids .
[ Sobbing ]
[ Bell Ringing ]
There 's no band practice today . There 's no anything today .
It 's surreal , right ? When just one person dies in Devil 's Kettle , it 's like time stops .
Feel guilty just breathing .
Word .
Chip , I need to tell you something kinda weird .
It 's about Jennifer . what ?
You know how last night we were talking , and someone came to my house ? It was Jennifer .
She looked like she had been beaten up or shot or something .
And then she barfed up this , like , disgusting , prickly stuff ...
that looked like roadkill and , like , sewing needles mixed together .
Yuck .
Well , she probably just inhaled a whole bunch of smoke or something .
No , Chip . No , it was like —
It was , like , evil .
Needy , I think you might wanna talk to the school shrink .
I 'm not saying that to be a dillhole .
Chip , I don 't tell whoppers , and I 'm not crazy .
I didn 't say you were crazy .
It 's just , everybody 's a little messed up about this , and it 's okay to feel —
Discombobulated ? Yeah . Fucked up .
Hey , Needy .
- Oh , hi , Colin . - I heard you were there last night in the fiery trenches .
Yeah .
Well , I 'm glad you didn 't die .
- Thanks . - Seriously .
How are you friends with Colin Gray ?
I thought Colin Gray only talked to the Dead Girls .
I just am . We have Creative Non-fiction together .
He 's a really good writer . He 's , like , all dark and emotional and stuff .
Oh . Well , I 'm like that too . I mean , I can relate .
You know , I 'm not all obvious about it like a poser .
Walk me home ?
You know it , babe .
♪ ♪ [ Hard Rock ]
[ woman Screaming ]
[ Man ] ♪ It 's all right ♪
♪ It 's all right ♪ ♪
Hi . Hey , Jennifer .
I 'm crazy sorry about your profound loss . [ Sniffles ]
You are crying about Craig , right ?
He was my best friend .
You know , I was there last night ,
and I was probably the last person to talk to him , like , ever .
Wow . You know what he said ?
Craig said that he always thought you and me ...
would make a totally banging couple .
Isn 't that just so weird ?
He — He said ' ' banging " ?
Feel my heart , Jonas .
I think it 's broken .
Mine too .
You come with me , just for a little while .
It 's what Craig would have wanted .
- Yeah . - Yeah .
[ Bird Squawking ]
You 're so warm . Why are you so warm ?
Shutties .
[ Cawing ]
[ Barking In Distance ]
[ Squawking ] Jennifer .
Jen . what ?
Look .
Mm-hmm .
[ Chuckles ]
They 're waiting .
Okay .
Mmm .
Do you miss Craig ?
Of course .
Well , you 're gonna see your buddy really soon .
What , you mean , like , in heaven someday ?
Nope .
[ Roaring ]
[ Jonas Screaming ] God .
[ Screaming Continues ]
Let it all out , kids .
[ Dog Barking ]
♪ ♪ [ Radio : Rock ] You want some baloney , Spector ?
[ Man on Radio ] And that was Low Shoulder , the local band ...
who became unlikely heroes of the tragedy in Devil 's Kettle last night .
Eyewitnesses say the boys helped numerous people escape the inferno ,
risking their own lives in the process .
That 's rock and roll with a conscience , ladies and gentlemen .
And guess what . We are honored to have Low Shoulder in the studio right now .
Now , how you guys holding ' up ?
[ Nikolai ] We 're maintaining , man .
It 's not easy , but , you know , the real heroes ...
are the people of Devil 's Lake .
I just hope we can convey 1 / 10th of their courage and spirit ...
on our upcoming album .
[ Bird Squawks ] [ Flies Buzzing ]
[ Gasps ]
Virgin mother .
♪ ♪ [ Radio : Woman Singing ] Crap .
You said it . Hey , Mom .
I didn 't know you were up .
Yeah .
Oh , God . I had another one of my night terrors .
Well , it 's 4 : 00 , so technically you had a day terror .
Right .
What 'd you dream about ?
I dreamed some bad people were trying to nail you to a tree ...
with hammers and big stakes and shit .
Just like J.C.
But I didn 't let ' em get you , 'cause I 'm a hard-assed , Ford-tough mama bear .
I can take care of myself .
Yeah , you say that ,
but one day you 're gonna be crying out for me , and I 'm not gonna be there .
[ woman Screaming , Crying ] No !
[ Man on TV ] Fatalities have grown in a horrific fire ...
that destroyed a popular local nightclub ... [ Cell Phone Rings ]
in Devil 's Kettle last night .
Yeah ? I feel so scrumptious !
Goody for you . You know when you kiss a boy for the first time ,
and it feels like your entire body is on vibrate ?
- Yeah ? - It 's that good .
Well , that 's nice .
Me , I 'm still a little bit depressed about , you know ,
the giant , smoldering funeral pyre in the middle of town .
[ Sighs ] Move-on-dot-org , Needy . It 's over .
Life is too short to be moping around about some white-trash pig roast .
That 's sweet , Jen .
You know , I tell it like it is .
And besides , you know what ?
You should be happy for me because I am having the best day ...
since , like , Jesus invented the calendar .
Jesus didn 't invent the calendar .
Whatever .
[ Beeps ] other line . Hold on .
- So blow it off . - It 'll just be a minute .
Pooh . I 'm crossing you out .
[ Beeps ] Hey .
I need to see you right now . I can barely hearyou .
♪ ♪ [ Toy Piano ] It 's because Camille is playing the piano .
Knock it off , Camille ! You knock it off !
Can you meet me at McCullum in 10 ?
You knock it off , Chip ! You 're a penis cheese !
[ Needy ] Uh , 15 ?
[ Woman ] ♪ Heard you 're new in town ♪
♪ want someone to show you round ♪
♪ well , no one knows this place just quite like me ♪ ♪
- I gotta go . - I am a god .
Okay . I gotta meet Chip in McCullum Park .
You know , Chip is looking really cute to me lately .
So , tell me , is he , uh , like , packing some serious pubic inches ?
What 's the story down there ?
I gotta go .
[ Siren wailing ]
[ Chattering ]
Why are the cops at your house ?
They 're not . They 're at Jonas Kozelle 's house .
Why ? He try to sell fake peyote to the eighth graders again ? No , Needy . He was murdered .
What ? Yeah .
Someone ripped Jonas limb from limb in the woods behind school .
They ate parts of him .
No one 's even supposed to know yet , but my dad just went over there and talked to the cops .
His mom is , like , catatonic .
She 's just staring out the front window like a zombie mannequin robot statue .
This can 't be a coincidence .
What are you talking about , Needy ?
A fiery death trap last night ,
and now a cannibal psycho takes down the biggest guy in school ?
Come on . It 's freaktarded .
Well , the bad luck 's gotta be over , right ?
I mean , it can 't get any worse , right ? It can 't .
I mean , you agree , right ?
You 're shaking .
Well , I 'm cold . It 's very cold out here .
You want my hoodie ?
[ Nikolai ] ♪ All alone in an empty room ♪
[ Needy Narrating ] The days marched on as usual ,
but most of us were too numb to enjoy ourselves .
Most of us .
♪ And I don 't know how we ended up here ♪
♪ I don 't know but it 's never been so clear ♪
♪ We made a mistake , dear ♪
[ Needy Narrating ] To the rest of the world , we were famous. we were saints .
our town 's only bar had burned to the ground ,
and our star linebacker was someone 's Snack Pack .
The whole country got a huge tragedy boner for Devil 's Kettle .
And the press , God ! They couldn 't get enough of our little world of shit .
[ Singing Along ] ♪ Through the trees ♪
♪ I will find you ♪
♪ I will heal ♪
♪ The ruins left inside you ♪
♪ ' Cause I 'm still here breathing now ♪
♪ I 'm still here breathing now ♪
♪ Until I 'm set free ♪
♪ Go quiet through the trees ♪ ♪
[ Needy Narrating ] Still , we were healing .
Like Chip , we figured things could only get better . Hey !
we had faith .
we were fucking idiots .
Before the period ends , I 'd like to make an announcement .
As you all know , today is the one month anniversary ...
of the tragedy at Melody Lane ...
and the murder ofJonas Kozelle .
[ Jennifer ] Boring . [ Girl ] Jesus !
what a bitch .
As I was saying , Jennifer and Needy ,
I finally have some good news to share with all of you .
The members of the rock and roll group Low Shoulder ...
have decided to extend a helping hand to our community .
As you all know , their song , ' ' Through The Trees , "
has become our unofficial anthem ...
of unity and healing . [ Sighs ]
And they have decided to release it as a benefit single .
Three percent of the profits will go to local families ...
who have been affected by loss .
What about the other 97 % ?
I mean , that 's just crass , right ?
' ' Crass . " It means greedy , exploitative , scummy .
Low Shoulder are American heroes .
No , they 're not ! I was there , Chastity .
They didn 't help anybody escape the fire .
I don 't even know how that rumor got started .
Rumor ? Rumor ?
It 's true . It 's on the Wikipedia .
we wouldn 't even know who they were if they hadn 't been playing that night .
- They used us . - You take that back , Needy Lesnicki .
- Girls — - We need them now more than ever .
- That 's enough . - [ Bell Rings ]
I 'm already sick of that song .
Yeah , it 's really poorly produced .
Could the bass be any lower in the mix ?
No offense , but you look really tired .
Is everything okay ? No . I feel like boo-boo .
My skin is breaking out , and my hair is dull and lifeless .
God . It 's like I 'm one of the normal girls .
Are you P.M.S.-ing or something ' ? P.M.S. isn 't real , Needy .
It was invented by the boy-run media to make us seem crazy .
Don 't look at me like that !
It 's just wearing off or something .
What 's wearing off ?
Hello , Needy . Hi .
Jennifer . Hi , Colin .
Can I borrow your English homework again ? I forgot to read Hamlet .
Is he gonna fuck his mom ?
No — I don 't — I don 't — I don 't think so .
Um , I actually wanted to ask you something .
You wanna know if I 'll go out with you ? No !
Yeah . What ? I —
- I don 't g — How 'd you know ? - Just go ahead with the pitch .
okay . Um —
Well , we 've been having a lot of fun in class , you and I ,
and I thought that maybe you 'd like to go see a movie or something .
There 's a , uh , midnight showing of Rocky Horror at the Bijou next weekend .
I don 't like boxing movies .
Yeah , but it 's no — It 's not a ... fucking boxing movie .
Um , fuck it . Okay . Forget it .
- That was random . - I 'm used to boys asking me out , Needy .
Colin 's really nice .
He 's into maggot rock . He wears nail polish .
My dick is bigger than his . I think he 's really cool .
You do ? Yeah .
Wait . Colin .
Why don 't you just come by my place tonight ?
I just got Aquamatine on DVD . It 's about this girl who 's , like , half-sushi .
I guess she has sex through her blowhole or something .
Okay .
[ Chuckles ] Great , yeah .
Okay . I 'll text you my address .
Cool .
Hi . Hey .
Mmm . Hi , Chip . [ Chuckles ]
Hey , hey . Ugh .
Get a room .
So , talking to your mysterious pal Colin Gray again .
No . He was asking Jennifer out on a date . That 's weird .
So are you gonna come over tonight ? Sure , I 'd like that .
I went to SuperTarget and picked up more condoms , so —
Thanks . Not that that has anything to do with —
Oh , no , I didn 't assume that . Well , I 'm —
Okay . I 'll see you tonight then .
Okay .
[ Man ] ♪ The roads are wrapped around your waist ♪ It 's for ambience .
♪ They lead me place to place ♪ It 's Jammin ' Jasmine .
My mom has Holiday Scents , too , if you 're —
This is nice . ♪ In fact , I made a career out of it ♪
♪ I 've always thought the left was your strongest side ♪
♪ But when it comes to you now I can 't decide ♪
♪ It 's only a matter of ♪
♪ Time ♪ ♪
♪ ♪ [ Hard Rock ]
[ Blubbering ]
[ Singing Along ] ♪ I can see clearly now the rain has gone ♪
♪ I can see all obstacles in my way ♪
♪ Gone are the dark clouds that had me blind ♪
♪ It 's gonna be a bright bright sunshiny day ♪
♪ I think I can make it now the rain has gone ♪
♪ All of the bad feelings have disappeared ♪
♪ Here is the rainbow I 've been prayin ' for ♪
♪ It 's gonna be a bright bright sunshiny day ♪ ♪
♪ ♪ [ Stops ] [ Engine off ]
[ Rattling ]
Hello .
♪ ♪ [ Faint ]
Jennifer ?
[ Man ] ♪ I know you seen me looking at you and you already know ♪
♪ I wanna love you love you ♪
♪ You already know ♪
[ Squawking ]
Wait. wait , wait , wait , wait .
' ' Slippery Swirl " ?
Yeah , it 's , uh , supposed to make it feel good for the girl .
[ Chuckles ] Cool .
♪ Baby , you got a phatty the type I like to marry ♪
♪ wanting ' to just give you everything and that 's kinda scary ♪
♪ ' Cause I 'm lovin the way you shake your ass ♪
♪ Bouncin' Got me tippin ' my glass ♪
[ Creaking ] ♪ Normally don 't get caught up too fast ♪
♪ Got a thing for you ♪
♪ I see you winding ' , grinding ' ♪
♪ Up on that floor ♪
♪ I know you see me looking at you ♪
♪ And you already know ♪
♪ I wanna love you love you ♪
♪ You already know ♪
Oh . [ Latex Snaps ]
♪ I wanna love you love you ♪
♪ You already know , girl ♪ ♪
You made it . [ Gasps ]
What 's going on ?
This , uh —
This isn 't really your house , is it ?
No , baby .
This is our house , just for you and me .
We can play Mommy and Daddy .
Do you even know my last name ? [ Chuckles ]
Silly .
I 've been sending you signals all year .
Couldn 't you tell ?
You give me such a wettie .
Put it in .
[ Exhales ]
- [ Squeaking ] - Jennifer !
What ? Are you scared ?
I thought boys like you were really into vermin and death and shit .
[ Zipper Unzipping ] Here you go .
Nice hardware , ace .
[ Bed Frame Squeaking ]
No way .
Ow ! Shit ! ooh ! Puncture wound .
God , that 's so emo .
[ Bones Snapping ] [ Screaming ]
I need you frightened .
[ Creaking Continues ] [ Moaning ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Gasping Loudly ]
[ Gasping Continues ]
I need you hopeless .
[ Shrieking ]
Hopeless .
[ Screaming ]
[ whispers ] Hopeless .
Hopeless .
[ Gasping ]
- [ Screaming ] - What ? what ?
What ?
Am I hurting you ?
Am I too big ?
What ?
[ Panting ] Needy . What 's wrong ?
Is it something I did ?
[ Squeaking ]
[ Slurping ]
[ Whimpering ]
[ Engine Starts ] [ Stereo ] ♪ Through the trees ♪
[ Screams ] ♪ I will — ♪
[ Sobbing ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Panting ]
Mommy ? Mommy !
[ Panting Continues ]
[ Sobbing ]
Are you scared ?
♪ ♪ [ Music Box : Distorted ]
[ Exhales ]
Hi . [ Gasps ]
- [ Screaming ] - God , Needy , enough with the screaming !
You 're such a cliché . Get out !
But we always share your bed when we have slumber parties .
I 'm not gonna bite you .
Is that my Evil Dead T-shirt ?
[ Moaning ]
What the fuck is happening ?
[ Laughing ] My God , Needy .
I have never heard you drop the F-bomb before .
I saw you ! I saw - I saw - I saw the — [ Imitates Stammering ]
Slow down , tardy slip . You sound like a sped .
I 'm gonna call the police . okay .
Why don 't you narc me out ?
I have the cops in my back pocket , Needy .
I 'm fucking a cadet . Remember ?
What do you want from me ?
Just want to explain some things to you .
Besides , best friends don 't keep secrets .
Right ?
So , you remember the night of the fire ? I got really messed up .
And those guys from Low Shoulder - totally evil .
They 're basically , like , agents of Satan ...
with really awesome haircuts .
♪ ♪ [ Rock Ballad ]
[ Jennifer ] where - Where are we going ?
You don 't have to talk if you don 't want to .
[ Man ] ♪ All right , dear Have a nice year ♪
♪ Teach the mean girls ♪
♪ How to be feared ♪
Are you guys rapists ?
- ♪ ♪ [ Continues ] - Oh , God , I hate girls .
♪ You could be satisfied ♪
Are you even sure if she 's a fucking virgin , man ?
Yes . Yes , I 'm a virgin . I 'm a virgin .
I 've never even done sex . I don 't know how .
So you guys should find somebody who does ...
know how .
See , Dirk ? I told you , man . You owe me a beer .
- what did they do to you ? - Just let me finish .
♪ ♪ [ Continues ] So they drove me out to the falls ...
and I kept looking for a way to escape , but it 's really dark out there .
[ Engine Stops ]
[ Screams ] Where are you going ? Huh ?
We got a waxing moon tonight , you guys , just like the ritual says .
Please !
No ! Please ! [ Screaming Continues ]
Do one of you guys have something to shut her up with ?
[ Sobbing , Screaming ]
Great . But get it nice and tight , though , 'cause I don 't wanna get fuckin ' clawed .
[ Groaning , whimpering ]
I don 't know if we should go through with this .
[ Sighs ] Dirk .
Do you wanna work at Moose Hoof Coffee forever ? I don 't , okay ?
Do you wanna be a big loser , or ...
do you wanna be rich and awesome ...
like that guy from Maroon 5 ?
Maroon 5 .
Okay . That 's what I thought .
Go and fetch me the ritual , brother .
okay . [ Mouths Words ] What the fuck ?
Thank you . [ Clears Throat ]
- All right . - That 's it ?
Yeah . I found it online .
' ' we come here tonight to sacrifice the body of " —
What is your name again ? Tiffany ?
My name is Jennifer . Super .
' ' we come here tonight to sacrifice the body of Jennifer from Devil 's Kettle . "
Please , please . Please , please , don 't do this .
I 'll do anything . I 'll do anything you want .
[ Sighs ]
Do you know how hard it is to make it as an indie band these days ?
There 's so many of us , and we 're all so cute ...
and it 's like , if you don 't get on Letterman ...
or some retarded soundtrack , you 're screwed , okay ?
Satan is our only hope .
we 're in league with the beast now , and we have to make a really big impression on him .
And to do that , we 're going to have to butcher you and bleed you .
And then Dirk here 's gonna wear your face .
Relax . I 'm kidding about the face . The rest is gonna happen though .
But you know what ? Maybe we 'll write a song about you . As a fan , that 'd be cool , right ?
[ Sobbing , whimpering Continue ] [ Clears Throat ]
No ! No ! with the deepest malice ,
we deliver this virgin unto thee .
Dude , that is a hot murder weapon . It 's a bowie knife .
Bowie ? Nice .
- Here we go ! It 's gonna be gnarly ! - No , please , please !
No , please , God ! wait a second . I just thought of something .
Jenny , Jenny , you 're the girl for me .
You don 't know me , but you make me so happy .
I tried to call you before , but I lost my nerve .
[ All Singing ] ♪ I used my imagination ♪
♪ But I was disturbed ♪
♪ Jenny , I got your number ♪
♪ I need to make you mine ♪
♪ Jenny don 't change your number ♪
- ♪ 867-5309 ♪ - [ Screaming ]
♪ 867-5309 ♪
[ Screaming , Sobbing ]
They killed you .
[ Scoffs ] I 'm still here , aren 't I ?
They did go all Benihana on my ass with that knife and it should have killed me ,
but for some reason it didn 't .
Maybe it did .
[ Splashes ]
[ Jennifer ] Anyway , I don 't really remember what happened after that .
I just know that I woke up and I found my way back to you .
I remember .
I couldn 't bring myself to hurt you .
I mean , I 'm a really good friend ,
but I was just so hungry .
[ Coughing ]
[ Coughs ]
Ahmet .
You made it out . [ Coughs ]
Are you lost ?
Does your host family know you 're alive ?
Does anyone know you 're alive ?
You come with me .
We 're gonna sort all this out , okay ?
And ever since then , I just knew what I had to do to be strong .
And when I 'm full , like I am right now ,
I 'm , like , unkillable .
Like , I can do shit like this. watch . [ Gasps ]
It 's really cool . Just watch . Look .
It 's , like , some X-Men shit , right ?
What do you mean , when you 're full ?
What about my mom 's Kia ? Why were you covered in blood ?
You didn 't even look human .
You know , Needy , maybe you should talk to somebody about these ...
disturbing thoughts that you 're having .
we 're all really concerned .
Especially Chip .
I think he may be having second thoughts about you .
Leave . Come on , Needy . Let me stay the night .
We can play boyfriend-girlfriend like we used to .
What are you doing ? Um , you said to leave .
See you at school .
We are gathered here to celebrate the life of Colin Gray ,
who was plucked from the prime of his youth .
[ woman Sobbing ]
No ! No !
[ Needy Narrating ] They did a big memorial assembly for Colin at school .
And we had to watch another presentation about curfews and the buddy system ...
and how to deal with grief .
But nobody seemed to care anymore .
Sorrow was last week 's emotion .
Sure , we all hoped this would be the last funeral ,
but I knew better .
So I did some research .
Paranormal research .
' ' offering a virgin to Satan . "
' ' If the sacrifice is impure -
Human and demonic relations " —
' ' Destroying a demon .
' ' Demons are weakest when hungry ,
but a blade to the heart is the surest way to kill the beast . "
Jennifer and I hadn 't spoken since our encounter in my room .
Actually , I hadn 't really spoken to anyone .
Hey .
Just bought our formal tickets .
Did you make reservations at the Cheesecake Factory ?
Chip , I can 't go to the dance with you .
What ? Why ?
Look , just trust me . You shouldn 't go at all .
what are you talking about ? Not here .
What 's going on ? You 're breaking up with me ?
Please , Chip ! I just need to show you something .
Is this about Jennifer ? Yes !
But I promise you this is the last thing — Needy , I care about you . A lot .
As a person , not just some girl I made love to for four minutes the other night .
And I 'm scared of what 's happening to you . You 're acting really fucked up .
Please just let me show you .
[ Exhales ] Okay .
Jennifer 's evil .
I know .
No , I mean , she 's actually evil .
Not high-school evil .
I 've been through the occult section at the library five times .
Our library has an occult section ?
Yeah , it 's um — it 's really small .
Uh , you have to read this .
' ' Demoni " — ' ' Demonic transference . "
It 's something that happens when you try to sacrifice a virgin to Satan ...
without using an actual virgin .
The guys in the band tried to sacrifice her in the woods .
But what they didn 't know is that she hasn 't been a virgin since junior high .
It all makes sense now . Read this .
' ' If the human sacrifice is impure , the result may still be attained ,
' ' but the demon will forever reside in the soul of the victim .
She must forever feed on flesh to sustain the demon . "
- Okay . - She 's eating boys !
They , like , make her really pretty and glowy ...
and her hair looks amazing .
And then when she 's hungry , she 's weak and cranky and ugly .
I mean , like , ugly for her .
Don 't you get it ?
The dance .
It 'll be like an all-you-can-eat buffet .
Needy , I think you need help .
oh , my God . You don 't believe me .
It 's not that I don 't believe you . I just don 't believe this .
God ! This is a nightmare !
Well , what about the dance ?
Who cares about the goddanged dance , Chip ?
I do . I ordered your corsage .
It 's an orchid . It was , like , $ 12 .
I 'll be at the dance . I just need to keep an eye on Jennifer .
Promise me you 're not gonna go .
Needy , I — I 'm not your guy anymore ?
Chip , it 's not safe for us to be together right now .
[ Woman ] ♪ You hit me once I hit you back ♪
♪ You gave a kick I gave a slap ♪
♪ You smashed a plate over my head ♪
♪ Then I set fire to our bed ♪
♪ You hit me once I hit you back ♪
♪ You gave a kick I gave a slap ♪
♪ You smashed a plate over my head ♪
♪ Then I set fire to our bed ♪
♪ Ohh-oh-oh ♪
♪ You hit me once I hit you back ♪
♪ You gave a kick I gave a slap ♪
♪ ♪ [ Continues ] [ Needy Narrating ] All over Devil 's Kettle ,
kids were getting ready for the dance ,
blissfully ignorant that some poor chump ...
was on his way to being Satan Chow .
[ Man ] ♪ Yeah , whoo-ooh-ooh ooh-ooh ♪
♪ ♪ [ Continues ] [ Knock On Door ]
In my underpants , Mom ! I need to give you something .
What , Mom ?
Ladies ' pepper spray ?
There 's obviously a sicko out there who likes boys .
Mom , I can take care of myself . I 've been using the Bowflex .
Did you hear what Colin Gray looked like when they found him ?
Lasagna with teeth ? You heard .
♪ ♪ [ Continues ]
[ Exhales ] You picking Needy up at her house ?
Um , I 'm meeting her at the dance .
I want pictures with your sister before you go .
Yes , ma 'am .
[ Man ] ♪ Stop there and let me correct it ♪
♪ I wanna live a life from a new perspective ♪
♪ You come along because I love your face ♪
♪ And I 'll admire your expensive taste ♪
♪ And who cares Divine intervention ♪
♪ I wanna be praised from a new perspective ♪
Okay , one more . Back to back .
Big smiles . Cheese !
♪ ♪ [ Fades ]
♪ ♪ [ Rock ]
[ Man ] ♪ I wonder what keeps us so high up ♪
♪ ♪ [ Continues , Faint ]
[ Dog Howling , whimpering ]
♪ Keep very quiet and cling to my mouth as I 'm cryin ' ♪
♪ So frightened of dyin Relax , yes , I 'm tryin ' ♪
♪ But fear 's got a hold on me ♪
♪ Yes , this fear 's got a hold on me ♪
- okay , can we all — - [ Feedback ]
♪ Yes , this fear 's got a hold on me ♪ ♪ Quiet down , please .
Uh , boys , thankyou .
Welcome to the Spring Formal !
[ Students Cheering ]
[ Bird Calling ]
[ Gasps ] Didn 't you hear me calling your name ?
You weren 't calling my name .
Yes , I was .
I-I couldn 't hear it .
Listen , I need to talk to you about you-know-who .
Our little Needy .
I hope everybody has had an opportunity ...
to consume some of the pecan sandies and Cran-Grape ...
that were so generously donated by the parents club .
[ Applause ] Yeah !
But the real treat is yet to come .
She 's been acting a little off lately .
[ Sighs ]
Look , I think I know what 's wrong with her .
What ? What is it ?
You know how Needy has been really upset since Colin Gray died ?
Mm-hmm .
Well , it 's not just because he was , like , brutally murdered and stuff .
I don 't wanna say this ! Say it .
Needy and Colin were intimate .
And by that ...
I mean they were porking on a semi-regular basis .
No .
She and Colin were doing things that you have never even heard of .
Okay ? Total varsity moves .
I just can 't believe that she would mess with your head like this .
I care about you so much , Chip .
More than I 've ever had the guts to admit .
These fine young gentlemen ...
have been generous enough to take time out ...
from their sold-out national tour ...
to play our dance for free .
Needy didn 't deserve a boy like you .
Boys and girls , please welcome ...
Low Shoulder !
♪ All alone in an empty room ♪
♪ Nothing left but the memories ♪
♪ Of when ♪
♪ I had my best friend ♪
Oh , you 're so salty .
Yeah , you 're ... salty too .
Say it like you mean it .
Say I 'm better than Needy .
What ? Why ?
♪ Take my breath ♪
♪ As your own ♪
♪ And take my eyes ♪
♪ To guide you home ♪
♪ ' Cause I 'm still here breathing now ♪
♪ I 'm still here breathing now ♪
♪ And I 'm still here ♪
Chip .
♪ ' Cause I 'm still here breathing now ♪
♪ I 'm still here breathing now ♪
♪ And I 'm still here now ♪
♪ ' Cause I 'm still here breathing now ♪
♪ I 'm still here breathing now ♪
♪ And I 'm still here ♪ ♪ I 'm still here ♪
♪ And you 're not coming back ♪ ♪
[ Switch Clanking ] [ Electricity Buzzing ]
Mmm .
[ Fly Buzzing ]
What are you doing ?
[ Fly Continues Buzzing ] Swimming .
Ha-ha .
Come on , Chip .
Show me your breast stroke .
[ Sighs ]
I feel so empty .
Yeah , me too .
Why don 't you just come here and kiss me again ?
I can 't .
I 'm sorry .
This just feels weird .
[ Gasping ]
[ Groans ]
Help !
[ Shrieking ] Needy .
[ Screaming ]
[ Gasping , Coughing ]
Needy .
[ Screaming ]
[ Gagging ]
She can fly ?
She 's just hovering . It 's not that impressive .
God , do you have to undermine everything that I do ?
You are such a player-hater .
You 're a jerk .
Wow . Nice insult , Hannah Montana .
You got any more harsh digs ?
You know what ? You were never a good friend .
Even when we were little , you used to steal my toys ...
and pour lemonade on my bed .
And now I 'm eating your boyfriend .
See ? At least I 'm consistent .
Why do you need him ? Huh ?
You could have anybody that you want , Jennifer .
So ... why Chip ?
Is it just to tick me off ?
Or is it because you 're just really insecure ?
I 'm — I am not insecure , Needy .
God , that 's a joke . How could I ever be insecure ?
I was the Snowflake Queen .
Yeah . Two years ago , when you were socially relevant .
I am still socially relevant .
And when you didn 't need laxatives to stay skinny .
I am going ...
to eat your soul ...
and shit it out , Lesnicki !
- Thought you only murdered boys . - I go both ways .
[ Gasps , Groaning ]
[ Groaning Continues ] Ow .
[ Screams ]
[ Exhales ]
You got a tampon ?
Thought I 'd ask .
You seem like you might be plugging .
[ Chip Moaning ]
[ Sobbing ]
Oh , Chip .
Needy .
I should have believed you .
I 'm sorry .
No . No , no . Listen to me . I 'm gonna get some help . Okay ?
Okay ? Yeah. okay .
[ Coughing ]
[ Gasps ]
It 's not working .
[ Banging Phone on Cement ] Fuck !
- Come on ! - Hey , hey .
I 'm going somewhere .
No , no , no . You 're not going anywhere . Yes , I am .
I think I already died before you got here , but I woke up when I heard your voice .
I love you .
I love you too .
And you look totally hot in that dress .
Oh , you 're clearly delirious .
No , I 'm not .
Oh , Ch — No !
[ Screaming ] No !
No !
[ Sobbing Continues ]
[ Man on TV ] Abduction and adduction , right ?
Inner and outer . But you know what 's really important ?
Hurdle or sprint . That 's huge .
Say I wanna do just my hip flexors or my buttocks even more .
I do what 's called digging . I use this for a lot of swimwear models .
Very , very , very important . How about Butt Squeeze ?
Yeah , I see you wanted to touch . Not this show ! Not touching this show !
okay . And of course -
[ TV : Off ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Grunting , Yelling ]
Best friends forever , huh ?
You killed my fucking boyfriend , you goddamn monster !
You dumb bitch !
[ Groans , Screams ]
Mmm !
You know what this is for ? Huh ?
It 's for cutting boxes .
[ Groaning ]
Do you buy all your murder weapons at Home Depot ?
- God , you 're butch . - [ Yells ]
Cross out Jennifer .
[ Groaning ]
[ Laughter ]
[ Grunts ] [ Moans ]
My tit .
No . Your heart .
[ Exhales ]
Jennifer , what is it , baby ?
Needy ?
[ Grunts ] oh , my God .
- oh , my God ! - [ Gasps ]
Oh , God !
[ Exhales ]
[ Sobbing ]
I don 't know who Needy Lesnicki is anymore .
[ Sniffing ]
I 'm a different person now .
A person who uses curse words and kicks orderlies ...
and sees things that aren 't there .
A very bad , very damaged person .
But sometimes change can be good .
For instance , most occult scholars don 't know this ,
but if you 're bitten by a demon and you live ,
you just might absorb some of the demon 's abilities .
You just might get lucky for once in your miserable life .
[ Crash , Fence Rattling ]
Where are you looking to go , young lady ?
East , towards Madison .
Hop in my chariot .
So , why are you headed east ?
I 'm following this rock band .
[ Chuckles ]
Must be one hell of a group .
Tonight 's gonna be their last show .
♪ ♪ [ Rock ]
[ Woman ] ♪ And the sky was made of amethyst ♪
♪ And all the stars are just like little fish ♪
♪ You should learn when to go ♪
♪ You should learn how to say no ♪
♪ Might last a day , yeah ♪
[ Fans Clamoring , Chattering ]
♪ Mine is forever ♪
♪ when they get what they want ♪
♪ They never want it again ♪ [ Bell Dings ]
♪ well , they never want it again ♪
♪ Go on , take everything ♪ And he 's fucking out !
♪ Take everything I want you to ♪ Candy chest .
♪ Go on , take everything ♪
♪ Take everything I want you to ♪
Look at this motherfucker ! Don 't be filming ' this . [ Doorbell Rings ]
Listen , go get the door . That 's a sharp table knife you got .
Get the fuck out of here . ♪ Go on , take everything ♪
♪ Take everything Take everything ♪
♪ Take everything ♪ ♪
♪ ♪ [ Rock Ballad ]
[ Man ] ♪ Darling Darling , darling ♪
♪ I can 't wait to see you ♪
♪ A picture ain 't enough ♪
♪ I can 't wait to touch you ♪
♪ In the flesh ♪
♪ Darling Darling , darling ♪
♪ I can 't wait to hear you ♪
♪ Remembering your love ♪
♪ Is nothing without you ♪
♪ In the flesh ♪
♪ In the flesh In the flesh ♪
♪ Ohh-oh , ohh-oh ♪
♪ Ohh-ohh-oh ♪
Oh , my God ! I can 't wait !
[ All Chattering ] They 're here !
[ Girls Screaming ]
♪ Do it , do it , do it , do it Do it , do it , do it now ♪
♪ Say it , say it , say it , say it Say it , say it , say it now ♪
♪ Instead of carving up the walls ♪
♪ why don 't you open up We 'll talk ♪
♪ I am ready I am ready for a fall ♪
♪ Instead of carving up the walls ♪
♪ why don 't you open up We 'll talk ♪
♪ We are ready we are ready for the floor ♪
♪ I can 't hear your voice Do I have a choice ♪
♪ You 're sinking below I 'm using my force ♪
♪ Instead of carving up the walls ♪
♪ why don 't you open up We 'll talk ♪
♪ We are ready we are ready for the floor ♪
♪ Do it , do it , do it , do it Do it , do it , do it now ♪
♪ Say it , say it , say it , say it Say it , say it , say it ♪ ♪
♪ ♪ [ Electronic Vocalization ]
[ Man ] ♪ okay , now , one , two , three ♪
♪ You 've got me on my knees ♪
♪ And there 's blood on the ground ♪
♪ You keep me hanging around the crime scene ♪
♪ He is not hard to name ♪
♪ Go on and take a bite ♪
♪ And chew me up I just want a taste ♪
♪ when you spit me out Put me in my place ♪
♪ So chew me up It 's written on your face tonight ♪
♪ I give myself for you ♪
♪ Nothing left to lose ♪
♪ well , you chew me up ♪
♪ ' Cause , baby all I want is you ♪
♪ Tonight ♪ ♪
♪ ♪ [ Rock ]
♪ She 's got a target painted on her back ♪
♪ And keeps a list of the qualities a good girl lacks ♪
♪ She bites her lip ♪
♪ And sips her bottle ♪
♪ I take a drink 'cause the truth is hard to swallow ♪
♪ ohh-ohh ♪
♪ Sex and white lies Handcuffs and alibis ♪
♪ She lays her halo on the pillow where she sleeps ♪
♪ Her heart beats red wine ♪
♪ My toxic valentine ♪
♪ Lays her halo on the pillow that used to be ♪
♪ Sex and white lies Handcuffs and alibis ♪
♪ She lays her halo on the pillow where she sleeps ♪
♪ Her heart beats red wine ♪
♪ My toxic valentine ♪
♪ Lays her halo on the pillow that used to be ♪
♪ She lays her halo on the pillow ♪
♪ That used to be mine ♪ ♪